I'm in Tokyo, Japan.
It almost melts in your mouth. It's not
super fishy.
>> That's a steal.
>> Betrayal. Betrayal.
Here we go.
Today, I'm going to take you with me to
all the tourist hot spots. Right now, I
am at Tsukiji Fish Market, which is one
of the most famous fish markets in the
whole world. It's only 9:00 a.m. and
it's already packed. Let's go check it
out.
Let's get in line. Some tuna, fresh
tuna.
Hi.
For here, please.
Two. Yep.
This is the most popular thing in the
market, the viral fatty tuna. It's an
extra special experience for me because
it's my first piece of sushi in Japan
ever. I'm very excited. It's so fresh.
They slice it right in front of you.
They give you three different cuts of
tuna.
I'm using chopsticks
and dipping it in soy sauce.
It almost melts in your mouth. Wow. Very
delicious
high-end tuna. I love it.
Two plain, please. Yes.
The next thing I'm trying is tamagoyaki,
which is a rolled up fluffy omelet, and
they serve it on a skewer.
Woah, I love eggs, so I think I'll love
this as well.
Ooh, I always think of egg as a savory
food, but this is quite sweet.
Mhm, I need to take a photo of this.
Sorry, excuse me.
Ooh,
it's time to break out the fan. I'm
sweating.
Woah, if you're traveling to Japan in
the summer, bring one of these.
Two sirloin, please. Can we get wasabi,
too? Uh, oh, okay, thank you. Woah, look
at the char on it. Looks amazing. We got
wagyu skewers. It's [music] black
Japanese beef. I guess it's a very
special kind of beef. They have wasabi
in a squeeze bottle.
I'll try my first bite without the
wasabi.
Mhm,
very tender. So good, yes.
Yes, enjoy. I think I'll like it even
more with salt and wasabi.
All right, let's see.
Mhm.
Holy moly, that is good. Tender, greasy,
amazing. Should I share with the
cameraman?
I don't know. I think I could eat two of
these.
Okay, come on.
>> Woah, delicious, man. Crazy delicious.
Woah, this is like the best beef I've
ever had.
>> He's a tough critic, so that's how you
know it's good.
>> When I say good, it's like five out of
five.
>> I've always wanted to uni. To be honest,
I never really thought I would like it,
but I think Japan is the place to try
it.
Wow, it's very soft. It almost turns to
liquid and it's not super fishy. Very
good. Okay, let me try with the wasabi.
I like it.
Okay, my next stop is Asakusa. So, I'm
going to hop on the subway to get there.
Everything in Japan is so convenient. I
love that even in the subway station,
you can rent a charger or an umbrella.
The weather forecast said it's supposed
to rain later, so this might come in
handy.
We got our tickets and our change.
I made it to Asakusa. Let's explore
Sensoji Temple, which is the oldest
Buddhist temple in Tokyo. The street
leading to the temple is filled with
stalls selling food and souvenirs. I
heard that this soft serve is a must in
Japan. First taste of this iconic ice
cream.
Mhm.
It's almost a little bit sweet and
salty. And for the cone, it looks like
they use a cookie or a wafer of some
sort. This is the perfect treat to help
cool me down.
Princess treatment.
>> [music]
>> I'm going get my fortune told.
81 sounds like a lucky number to me. Now
I just find this.
Ooh,
that's got to be good fortune. It's at
the top. Okay, I'll read it and
summarize. Ooh, I think it's great. It
basically says that I'll be successful.
Wealth and fortune will [music] come to
me as I desire. Also, any difficulties
will change into happiness and I will be
very prosperous. [music]
Woohoo! I'm going to hang on to this.
>> Your fame will grow up higher among the
people.
>> You're trying to get famous? Are you
going to take over my channel?
>> Give me that
camera.
>> Betrayal. Betrayal. I feel reassured.
Gave me a good sense of positivity,
motivation, drive. Let's go.
Everyone on the internet is raving about
these fried sandwiches, so I'm going to
see if it's worth the hype.
Can I please get one creme brulee? Just
one is okay.
Yep. Thank you so much. This is
beautiful. They torched it.
It tastes like an elephant ear at the
fair. Well, this is actually so good.
Creme brulee was the right move.
I'm on Takeshita Street in Harajuku.
Let's go look around. There are so many
people here. Lots to see, lots to do,
lots to eat. Where do I begin? I stopped
in a store with all these little toy
vending machines. I want to buy
something cute here.
I'm running low on coins.
I thought about going with Hello Kitty
since it's so classic, but then I
stumbled upon these guys and [music]
they're so cute. I'm going to get one of
these.
Aw, it's cute.
How much is it? Is it in the budget?
Woo, that's pretty steep. All right, too
expensive to [music] take home with me.
I'm at Shibuya Crossing and there's just
a wall of people across from me. It's a
little scary. Here we go.
So many people are stopping in the
middle of the road and taking selfies. I
probably photo bombed so many people.
It's kind of surprising how short the
light is, especially considering it's a
major intersection.
Ooh.
I actually want to see this from above
next time. One more time?
>> Flying home, bye.
>> And you look tired.
We're packed in like sardines. Okay.
Here we go.
Wow, riding the subway in Tokyo during
rush hour is not for the weak. For me,
it was kind of a fun and exciting new
experience, but if you're
claustrophobic, I do not recommend.
I have a reservation.
For dinner, [music] we came to a
restaurant that specializes in eel. I
got a matcha highball to start.
Not bad. Not bad.
Thank you.
While ordering, I [music] actually asked
for less rice because that's an option
on the menu, but it's still [music]
huge. Little bit of rice and eel.
>> Really good. I think this is the
thickest eel I've ever had.
>> This is less than [music] 3,000 yen.
That's a steal.
They were so friendly. 10 out of 10.
Highly recommend that place. The food
was delicious. The vibe was great. I had
a unique cocktail. Perfect way to end
the day. Actually, I'm not ending the
day yet. I'm going to the Golden Gai for
a nightcap. Let's go.
There was a Don Quijote on the way,
[music]
so I had to stop in.
Oh my gosh, they have the melon.
This is my [music] favorite chocolate in
the world. We couldn't find it for a
long, long time, and here it is. [music]
It's got to be the melon flavor. It's
the best.
>> You got to buy this.
>> Okay.
Let's start with one today. I practiced
good self-control and only bought four
things. Mostly because I need to do some
more research before [music] coming back
again. I'm proud of myself.
Hi.
>> Hello.
>> Lumpia is 400.
>> I'm a brother-in-law from Michigan.
>> Really?
>> No way.
>> No What? That's crazy.
>> They're going to South Korea the first
time.
>> Oh.
>> Very nice.
Which one should we start with? This
one? Okay.
Okay.
No buy.
>> [screaming]
[laughter]
>> THAT IS SMOOTH.
YOU CAN TELL THAT'S MORE EXPENSIVE. I
like this one.
Bye.
That looks so good.
Okay, we'll try it. Yes. Thank you.
Thank you. Today was such an amazing
[music] day in Tokyo. Thanks for coming
along on the adventure with me. I'll see
you next time. Bye.